(Sheldon:)That's what my
train used to do.
(Bernadette:)Ready to call
tech support?
(Howard:)Give me the number.
(Howard:)Probably wind up
(Howard:)talking to some foreign guy
(Howard:)who's reading from
the same manual I have.
(phone ringing)
(Raj:)It's my father, you jerks.
(Raj:)Hello, Daddy.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)What did you say to your mother?
(Penny:)Nothing.
(Raj:)I was just calling to check in,
(Raj:)make sure she's doing okay.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)Well, after talking to you,
(Dr Koothrapalli:)she seems to think
I'm some sort of playboy.
(Leonard:)Really?
(Raj:)I don't know where
she'd get an idea like that.
(Raj:)You know Mummy
and her crazy imagination.
(Raj:)I'm so lucky I take after you.
(Dr Koothrapalli:)You think you take after me?
(Raj:)Well, I try to.
(Raj:)I certainly wouldn't
be a scientist